Uh, I was thinking about having some coffee.
あの私コーヒー飲もうと よもうと 思うんですけど ですけど
Who else wants some?
飲む人?
Oh, yeah. I forgot.
いっせい (一星)あつそうだ
Roast pork. I brought a whole one.
チャーシュ ナヤーンユ 塊ごと持ってきた
Wow!
(菜緒)おお!
I'll put it in your fridge.
(一星)冷蔵庫借りるぞ
Your room is really clean.
(一星)片付いてんな
You can change in here, but you sleep on the sofa.
うえはら (上原)着替えとかはここ使って 寝るのはソファ
I can sleep anywhere.
(一星)どこでもいいよ
All the other stuff is on that paper.
(上原)あと詳しいことは さつきの
Oh, you mean those rules on the fridge?
(一星)あああの 同居のルールってやつ?
Yeah.
仩原) うん
OK, I've got work now.
じゃあ俺 バイト行くけど
Don't pull any funny business.
変な気起こすなよ
-How boyfriend-like. -Shut up.
おー彼氏っぽい (上原)あのな
Thanks for letting me stay.
お世話になります
What's with you?
何だよあいつ
Oh, you're back.
(一星)おーお疲れ
I think Nao's still sleeping.
よしかわ 吉川まだ寝てるけど
Huh?
(EPT)
No need to rush home. I'm not going to do anything to her.
んな急いで帰ってこなくたって 何もしねえって
Who said I was rushing?
別に
Evening Star special pork roast fried rice
(一星) -一番星特製 焼き豚チャーハン
with wonton soup.
ワンタンスープ付き
-Wow! -Nice!
(菜緒,上原)お
Thanks.
(上原)いただきます
-Thank you. -My pleasure.
(菜緒)いただきます (- 85
This is better than I can do.
(菜緒)負けた
I'll cook for you guys while I'm staying here.
世話になる間飯は俺が作るよ
-Seriously? -What?
マジ? (菜緒)え?
Don't you dare tell my dad where I'm at, Nao.
吉川お前 親父に俺の居場所バラすなよ
I won't.
はーい
This is delicious, Issei.
いっちゃんおいしい
-Can I get seconds? -Yeah.
(上原)おかわりあんの? (一星)ある 上!
Thanks.
(菜緒) うんありがとう
You're used to this, aren't you?
いっちゃん慣れてるんだね
Of course I am.
(一星)当たり前だろ
-Next one. -Here.
(一星)貸して (菜緒)はい
-I'm not ready yet.
(一星)はえーよ いえ
OK.
(菜緒) うん
-Rinse it. -Look what you did!
(一星)流せば. 1)IL (菜緒)ほら せら 流ほ
There's onion still--
(菜緒) ネギついちやったじゃん
You can take a bath now.
お風呂入っていいよ
-Get to bed. -Huh?
(上原)お前もう寝ろよ (菜緒)え?
It's late.
(上原)もう遅いし
No, it's not.
いやまだ遅くないよ
-Come on. -I'm not sleepy either.
仩原)ほら (菜緒)眠くないし
I said go to bed.
寝ろって
-Why? It's not late. -That doesn't matter. Get to bed.
(菜緒)えつだから遅くないから (上原)いいから寝ろ寝ろ
I'm not sleepy at all. What're you doing?
(菜緒)眠くないし何でよ
-Do as I say. Get to bed. -No way! I'm not going to bed!
(上原)いいから寝ろってお前 (菜緒)だから寝ないよ
Hey! What're you doing?
(菜緒)ちょっ…ちょっと
You can take a bath first.
風呂お先に
Oh, OK. Thanks.
あつおお サンキュ
Time to get up!
(一星)起きろ!
This is way better than I can do.
(菜緒)あー負けた
Bon appétit.
(上原)いただきます
-Bon appétit.
(一星)いただきます (菜緒)いただきます
That's hot!
(一星)あっちい
-Hey, Issei. -Huh?
(菜緒)いっちゃん (一星)ん? っ? いん
-You've got bad bed head. -I do?
(菜緒)寝癖すごいよ (一星)え? 癖?
-Where's it funny? -Right here.
(一星)どこ? (菜緒) ここ どこ
-Turn that way. -Where is it?
あっち向いて (一星)どこだよ
-I said turn that way. -Ow! That hurt!
あっち向いてってば (一星)イッテお前
-I haven't even touched it. -I'm done.
(菜緒)何もしてないじゃん (上原)ごちそうさま
Huh? You're done eating already? You usually have three bowls of rice.
ん?もう食べないの? いつも3杯食べんのに
It's time to go.
(上原)時間だぞ
-Sorry. -It's OK.
(上原)悪いな (一星) うん
Oh! Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
ハツやT... ヤバいヤバいヤバい...
Forget about eating. Get going!
もういいから 早く行けよお前
Hurry up! You'll be late!
早く 遅刻だぞ
-Leave some for me. -OK.
残しとしてね (一星)ああ ねあ と)
Sorry, Issei.
(菜緒)ごめんねいっちゃん
-It's OK. -See you later.
(一星)ああ (菜緒)いってきます
Nao, can you lend me your house key?
(一星)吉川 家の鍵貸してくんねえか?
-My key? -Yeah.
(菜緒)鍵? (一生)のあ
It's not safe to go out without locking the door.
あの外出る時 鍵開いてたら物騒だろ I J
Oh, yeah. You're right.
(菜緒)あっそっか
OK.
ああ
Thanks.
サンキュー
Hey, wait for me!
ちよつ…ちょっと待って
-Bye! See you later. -Bye.
じゃあいってきます (一星)おう
Wait up for me, Uehara!
上原君待ってってば
Uehara!
上原君!
Wait for me, would you?
ちょっと待ってよ
Yu!
ゆう (まみ)優君
Aren't you going to talk to him?
(千崎)いいのか?会わなくて
Isn't that why you came?
会いに来たんじゃないの?
It's OK. I'll come back again later.
いいんだまたにする
Really? Issei?
(まりな)えついつちゃんが?
Yeah. He and his dad had an argument.
そうおやつさんと ケンカしたらしくて
But I'm partly to blame for it.
そのケンカの原因 半分は私のせいなんだけど
Two handsome guys... under one roof.
イケメン2人同じ屋根の下
Marina? Marina!
(光石) まりなまりな!
-Oh! I've got to go! -Why? That's just the first bell.
あっヤバい行かなきゃ (菜緒)え?まだ予鈴だよ
Haven't you heard? There's a university student here today.
何言ってんの 今日からでしょ大学生
-Really? -Yes! A student teacher!
(菜緒)へ? まりな)教育実習生!
I've got to go check him out.
早めにチェックしないと
Has she forgotten that I'm her boyfriend?
(光石)あいつ俺が彼氏ってこと 忘れてないか?
I wouldn't worry about it.
ドンマイ
I'm Senzaki Yu, a senior from Joso University.
じょうそう 城早大学4年の千崎優です
I'll be your teacher for the next two weeks.
今日から2週間 よろしくお願いします
Yes! He's hot!
しゃあイケメン!
Excuse me!
あの!
Nao, my girl!
菜緒ちゃん
Don't talk like that to me!
ちゃん付けは マズいんじゃないですか?
You are a teacher, after all.
先生だし 応
I'm so glad we could meet again, dear!
また会えてうれしいにゃん
I told you, quit talking like that!
だからそういうの やめたほうがいいんですよ
To be honest, I came here so I could see you.
ぶっちゃけ菜緒ちゃんに 会いにきたようなもんだから
What?
(菜緒)は?
Don't act so mean. Let's try to get along, OK?
そんな怖い顔しないで 仲良くしようよ
-Nao! -Cut that out!
仩原)吉川! (菜緒)やめて
Uehara.
(菜緒)上原君
Who's that?
仩原)誰?
He's the student teacher--
(菜緒)教育実習の 月天ーの...
I know exactly who you are!
俺は君のこと よーく知ってるよ の知
You're one of the top three hottest boys in school.
毎年御三家に選ばれる イケメンでありながら
Top of the class! Sportsman! An all-around awesome guy!
成績優秀スポーツ万能の 超ハイスペック男子
Twinkle, twinkle!
(千崎)キラキラ (菜緒)ヘヘヘ
-Oh, he's not that great. -Why are you all giggly?
それほどでもねえ (上原)何でお前が照れてんだよ
Sorry.
(菜緒)はい
So it's true. You two really are a couple.
本当なんだ 2人が付き合ってるって
Such a pity! I was so glad that I could see Nao again.
残念だなせっかく ふたなせつ 菜緒ちゃんと再会できたのに
I'm Senzaki Yu. I'll be working here for the next two weeks.
俺千崎優 2週間よろしくね
OK?
ね? a
What the hell is up with that guy?
何なんだよあいつは
He was in the same hospital as me.
入院してる時 同じ病院にいた人
So that's why he said "again." What an unfortunate coincidence.
それで再会って 偶然もいいとこだな こな
I was shocked to see him too.
私だってびっくりした
You didn't let slip about us to him, did you?
お前がヘラヘラ しゃべったんじゃないの?
What? Of course I didn't.
え?しゃべってないよ べつ
You know, you've been acting strange lately.
っていうか最近上原君 何か変
You're angry all the time.
怒ってばっかりだし 女又
That's because you're always letting your guard down.
あのなお前はいろいろと 隙が多いんだよ!
Like this morning...
今朝だって
This morning?
今朝?
Forget it.
もういい
-Miso ramen up! -OK!
(徹平)はいみそ上がり! (菜緒)あっはーい!
Here's your miso ramen. Enjoy!
(菜緒)みそラーメン てフ お待たせしましたどうぞ
-Excuse me! -One moment, please.
(客)すいません (菜緒)はい少々お待ちください
Damn him! Right when we're busy, too.
(徹平) まったく つに このクソ忙しい時に
Sorry, Nao. You have to work double hard because of that stupid son of mine.
(徹平)悪いね うちのバカ息子のせいで
Uhm, sir. About those bowls...
あのおやっさん 丼のことなんですけど
You see, it was me that broke them.
あれ割ったの私なんです
I ran into Issei while he was making the delivery.
配達中のいっちゃんと ぶつかっちゃつて 小
I'm very, very sorry.
本当にすいませんでした
Forget about it, Nao.
いいんだよ菜緒ちゃん
I already apologized to the customer. It's taken care of.
丼のことは先方に謝って 解決したんだ
But, didn't you have an argument about that?
いやでもケンカって...
He told me he wants to go learn somewhere else.
あいつよそで 修業したいとか言いだして
Really?
え?
He's gotten too big for his britches, saying he's leaving.
かわず 井の中の蛙で終わりたくねえとか 生意気言いやがって
How can I let him work somewhere else when he can't even do a proper job here?
うちの仕事も ろくにできねえ奴を
He told me so suddenly that I lost my temper and...
突然んなこと言われて 俺もカーッとなって思わず
Good night.
(菜緒)お疲れさまでした
Issei?
いっちゃん!?
Hi. What a coincidence.
おう 偶然だな
Yeah.
うん
Was it busy?
(一星)忙しかった?
-Why? Does it bother you? -No.
(菜緒)気になるの? (一星)別に
Really? Then I won't tell you.
あっそ じゃ教えなーい あじ
Now you're acting like Uehara.
お前そういうとこ 上原に似てきたよな
Really? You're kidding!
えっウソ
Like I said before, you'll become more and more like each other.
言ったろ 一緒にいると似てくるって
Like a married couple.
夫婦しかり
Oh, dear. Was I really being that mean?
(菜緒)どうしよう 私そんな意地悪かな?
Well, so I guess
あつじゃあやっぱ
your mom was a lot like your dad too, huh?
いっちゃんのお母さんも似てたの? おやつさんと
Not at all.
全然
She was at the shop every day.
毎日店いるのに
But she didn't smell of ramen.
全然ラーメン臭くなくてよ おふくろ
She just had a nice smell.
いい匂いがしてさ
So she ran the shop with him?
お母さんも一緒に お店やってたんだ
Yeah.
ああ...
The three of us were always together,
いつも3人でいたから
so ever since I can remember, I thought I'd inherit the shop.
俺も物心つく頃には 店継ぐもんだと思っててさ
But I want to make a name for myself.
俺一人前になりたいんだ
Dad learned the business at a lot of different shops.
親父がいろんな店で 修業してきたみたいに
I want to be like him and learn from different people
俺も1人になって 修業積んで
so I can be deserving enough to run Evening Star Ramen.
一番星の看板 守れるようになりたいんだ
You can do it, Issei! I'm sure!
いっちゃんならできるよ
I'm on your side.
私応援する
I'm sure your dad will understand if you talk it over with him.
ちゃんと話せば おやつさんも分かってくれるよ
He'll never listen to me. He's too stubborn.
聞く耳持たねえからなあ あの頑固親父
Don't worry. He'll listen.
大丈夫 大
Yeah, right.
あついや
When you say "Don't worry," it actually makes me worry.
吉川に大丈夫って言われると 不安
What?
(菜緒)え?
I'm home.
(菜緒)ただいま
Hi.
(菜緒) よいしよ (上原)おかえり
-We just happened to run into each other. -I wasn't asking.
たまたま 一緒になっただけだよ
Hey. I'll take you on.
おい勝負しようぜ
-Huh? -Really?
仩原)あ? (菜緒)え? 上菜
You guys are pretty bad at this.
2人とも弱いね
20 MINUTES LATER
ああ…
You guys still aren't done?
まだ終わんないの? なし
-Shut up.
(上原。一星)うるさい
-Time out. I've got to go to the bathroom. -OK.
ちょっとタイムトイレ (一星)おう
She's a really nice girl.
(一星)いい奴だよな
Don't you ever make her cry.
せんなよ
-Uno! -What?
ウノ! (一星)は?
Yes!
よっしゃあ! (一星)あ ああ
I lost!
負けた
You don't have to tell me that, you know.
仩原) 言われなくても分かってるよ
Come on, Nao. Let's go.
吉川帰るぞ
Oh, sorry.
あっごめん
I'm the class helper today, and I have to clean up the chem lab.
私今日日直で 理科室の道具片付けなきゃ
Then I have to go straight to work.
でそのまま まっすぐバイト
Bye.
うん
Thank you for helping me, Abe.
ごめんねあべっち 手伝ってもらっちゃつて
No problem. Today's an important day, after all.
(阿部) ううんいいよ 今日は大事な日だからな
Yeah. I appreciate it.
(菜緒) うんよろしくね
Yes! This is for him!
(菜緒)頑張ろう!
There's a total babe at the school gate!
(男子生徒1)校門の前に マジでかわいい子
She's wearing a Seiran High uniform!
(男子生徒2) 聖蘭女子の制服だよ! せいらん
Holy cow! What a babe! She's totally hot!
(男子生徒たち)マジかヤバい もう超かわいかったもん \かつに ソ
Damn, she's sweet!
超かわいい
Wow!
おお!
Oh!
ああつ!?
-No, no, no! -Huh?
(阿部)いやいやいや... (菜緒)わあ!
You shouldn't look. She's incredibly ugly. It'll hurt your eyes.
(阿部)見ないほうがいい すっごいブサイク目の毒
Let's clean this place up.
ねっ片付けよう
When you say something like that,
あべっちが べつ そんなこと言うなんて
-it makes me extra curious. -No!
余計気になる (阿部)いやいや…
-Let me see. -Seriously, don't.
(菜緒)見せてよ (阿部)やめとけって本当に
-Let me see! -No, don't.
(菜緒)見せてよ見せてよ (阿部)やめとけって
Let me see! Hah! Got past you!
(菜緒) み…見せてよ隙あり!
Huh? Who's that?
え?誰...
If my memory is correct, she's the one who made the beef stew.
俺の記憶が正しければ 肉じゃがの
King of ladies?
キングオブ女子?
Yes.
TIZ
Oh, I know what this is!
あつあれだ
They've got a class reunion.
クラス会がどうとか 言ってたから
I'm sure she's here about that.
その連絡だよきっと
Oh, is that why?
そうなんだ
It's all right.
大丈夫だって
I told you before, she's got a boyfriend.
言ったろ? あの子には彼氏がいるって
Oh, yeah.
そっか
Yeah, that's right.
そうだよね!
I didn't mean to bother you at school.
(まみ) ごめんね学校まで来ちゃって
But you never answer my texts.
上原君 全然返信くれないから
It's the class reunion info.
クラス会の案内状
Oh, yeah.
ああ
I'm going to my boyfriend's, so we're headed in the same direction.
彼のとこ行くから 同じ方向だね
Come on! Quit dragging your feet!
(千崎)はいはい ダラダラ歩かないで
-Pick up the speed. -Yes, sir.
さっさと歩く ! (エリカ·美南)はーい
-Who's that? -She's just an admirer.
(美南)何?あれ (エリカ)ただの追っかけっしょ こたの烜つ
It'll be fine. He'd never have anything to do with her.
大丈夫じゃね?上原君が 相手にするわけないじゃん
That Uehara sure is popular.
本当にモテるんだね 上原君って
That's because he's perfect in every way.
(美南)上原君は完璧なんです
-But he's got a girlfriend, right? -Yeah. Nao.
でも彼女いるよね (エリカ)ああ吉川?
But we haven't given up on him.
まあうちら認めてないんで
Yet they live together, right?
でも一緒に住んでるよね
-Really? -They do?
(美南)え? (エリカ)は?
How about near the station?
駅前とか?
-Are you on your way home, my dear? -Good bye!
(千崎)菜緒ちゃん今帰り? (菜緒) さようなら
There's no need to rush off. Your boyfriend seems busy anyway.
そんなに慌てなくてもいいじゃん 彼も忙しそうだし
He's cheating on you.
彼浮気してるよ
No, he's not!
してません!
Yes, he is. Just now he was--
してるよ今だってさ
You're mistaken! That was just--
勘違いです あれはただ
I'm not mistaken, I'm afraid.
勘違いじゃないよ 残念ながら
-What? -She's an old friend of mine.
え?
She's Momoyama Mami from Seiran High School.
聖蘭学園の桃山まみ
Really?
(菜緒)え...
She's been visiting Uehara's place.
あいつ上原のマンション 通ってるみたいだし
And she says she sees you around a lot too.
で菜緒ちゃんのことも よく見かけるって
Nao's his girlfriend, so of course she goes to his house sometimes.
そりゃ彼女ですから 家ぐらい行くでしょう
Right?
ねえ?
You're living together!
同棲
At least that's what the rumors say.
してるって噂本当?
Are they true?
ひさし 上原久志と
No... No, they're not. That's crazy.
し…してません そんなの
Even though you and Mami are quite different,
まつまみと菜緒ちゃん 結構タイプ違うけど
he's two timing you. A top three boy, but a typical male.
二股って... 御三家もただの男ってことだ
How can you say that? You don't know anything about him.
あなたに上原君の 何が分かるんですか?
I do know that he's a scumbag.
最低の奴だってことだけは こつC 分かるよ
Nao!
吉川
I wonder... if he really knows... that we're living together.
あの人知ってるのかな 同居のこと
He's just taking a shot in the dark because he heard that rumor.
当てずっぽうだろ 噂とか言ってたし
Don't worry about it.
気にすんなって よつ
Yeah, you're right.
そうだよね
Anyway, we've got things to do for Issei!
とにかく今日は いっちゃんのこと頑張らないと
Right?
ねっ! ねつ
Nao. Are you sure you're all right?
吉川大丈夫か?
I'm fine. Just fine.
大丈夫大丈夫!
I'm fine.
大丈夫 大
Seems like you're faking it.
(阿部)空元気って感じだな
I'm just fine!
大丈夫 大
I trust in Uehara, so I'll be fine.
私上原君のこと 信じてるから
Are you sure it's not "I want to trust him"?
“信じたい”じゃなくて?
Jeez, Abe! You sound like a therapist.
何?あべっち 何かカウンセラーの人みたい
-But, Nao, you seem-- -I told you, I'm fine!
だって吉川 (菜緒)大丈夫なの!
Let's stop talking about this.
もうこの話終了
Today's an important day, you know.
ほら今日は 大事な日なんだし
Thanks for helping me, Abe.
よろしくねあべつち
Uehara!
(ななこ)久志 ノひ. 八""
You've reached the answering service.
(アナウンス) 留守番電話に接続します
Darn it all! Why won't you answer when it's important?
ちょっ…もう 何で肝心な時に出ないのよ
Wow, Abe! He's done an amazing job!
あべっちすごい すごいよあベっち! べつ
Take one, please.
(阿部)お願いします お願いします
Evening Star Ramen coupons! Good today only!
人気ラーメン店一番星! 本日限り使える割引券でーす
Miso ramen up! Here you are.
(徹平)はいみそラーメン お待たせしました
Why so many people?
何でこんなに?
One miso ramen, three soy sauce ramens, one fried rice and pot stickers.
(菜緒)みそ一丁しょうゆ3丁 チャーハン餃子です
Coming right up!
あいよ!
If only Issei were here.
あついっちゃんが いてくれたらな
Forget about him. He's no use to me.
いねえ奴相手にしても 仕方ねえ
How about I give him a call?
あつめの いっちゃんに電話しましょうか?
Don't!
いい!
You'll be missing out if you don't try! The ever popular Evening Star Ramen!
今日食べないと損するよ 一番星大人気の一番星!
Thank you.
ありがとうございます お願いします
Wow! Look at this line!
(阿部)おおつすっげえ列
Thank you!
(菜緒) ありがとうございました
Here you are. Sorry for the wait.
ああすいません お待たせしました
Soy sauce ramen up!
はーいしようゆ上がり!
-Got it. -Huh?
あいよ (徹平)おっ
Which table?
どこ?
-Five. -Got it.
5番さん
Here you are.
はいお待ちどお
-Water on three, Nao. -OK.
(一星)吉川3番さんにお冷! (菜緒)はい
Clear the counter, Abe. Ow!
阿部カウンターの器下げて イテッ…
Yes, sir.
(阿部)はい
Now we're cooking!
ok-L
Who gave you permission to do this anyway?
ったくお前ら つた 勝手なことしやがって
Sorry.
(菜緒)ごめんなさい
Did you think I'd be forced to come back if the shop got busy?
店が忙しくなれば 俺がすんなり戻れると思ったわけか
Good idea, huh?
ナイスアイデアでしょ?
Ow!
イッタ… ツ
Nao.
菜緒ちゃん
Yes?
(菜緒)え?
Thanks for worrying about us.
ありがとね心配してくれて
Yeah, I guess you're right.
まあそうだな
Thanks to you, we know that this place is in trouble without me.
おかげでやっぱりこの店は 俺がいないとダメって分かったし
-You're wrong. -What?
(徹平)逆だよ (一星)え?
I'm never giving this shop to an irresponsible ass like you.
お前みたいな無責任な奴に 店は継がせねえ
What?
はあ!?
Get some practice at a bigger shop.
もっとでっかい店で 修業して来い!
If you don't, I won't ever let you run the Evening Star.
じゃないと 一番星の看板は譲れねえ
Dad...
親父
Manager...
おやつさん
It's just like you said.
おめえの言うとおり
It's probably important for you to work on your own for a while.
1人でやってみる時期も 大事なのかもしれないねえ
Go ahead.
やってみろ
Why are you looking like that?
(徹平)なんつー顔してんだよ
Since you were little, you were always by my side.
お前は小さい頃から 俺にまとわりついて
You kept saying you'd take over after me.
ここを継ぐって 言い続けてきたから
It was like your life was mine.
お前の人生俺のもん みたいなとこがあってな
But that's not right.
でも違うんだよね
I'm sorry about what I did.
悪かったな
Uhm...
あの…
I'm sorry for saying what I did too,
勝手言ってすいません
Dad.
…でした
-Thanks for today. -No problem.
(一星)おおお疲れ (菜緒)お疲れ おお
Nao, here.
(一星)あっ吉川 これ
I'll give it back to him.
返しとくね
I'll get my bag tomorrow.
荷物は明日にでも
OK. See you later.
(菜緒)分かったじゃあね
Nao!
EHJII
Uhm...
あのさ
Yes?
うん
Thanks.
ありがとな
Hello?
もしも~し
How come you haven't answered your phone?
(ななこ) あんた何で電話出ないのよ
What's up?
え?
-I made too much again. -Oh, but I, uh...
(まみ) また作りすぎちゃつて (上原)あつでも…
Don't you like fried chicken?
(まみ)あつから揚げ嫌い?
-Yes, I do. -Then here.
仩原)いや (まみ) じゃあ
It'll just go to waste.
余らせてももったいないし
Actually, I made it for him.
本当はねせっかく作ったのに
But he said he doesn't need dinner tonight.
彼に今日はご飯いらないって 言われちゃつて
OK, fine. Thanks.
分かった ありがとう つに
No problem.
(まみ) うん!
Oh. How's it going?
(上原)おっおかえり
Nao?
(上原)吉川?
Are you upset about something?
何か機嫌悪い?
Of course not!
違う!
Oh, I see.
あつそう
Nao.
上原)吉川 仩原)吉川
-I think-- -Who was that girl just now?
あのさ ご... (菜緒) さっきの人誰?
I thought you didn't like receiving things from girls.
だって上原君
But there's nothing I could do. She came to the door.
いや仕方ないだろ 家まで来られたら
You took her to your work too, right?
バイト先まで 連れてったんでしょ?
Nanako told you?
ななこか
So it's true.
本当なんだ
I've never even been there.
私も行ったことないのに
Don't be stupid.
アホくさ
This isn't stupid!
アホくさくない!
I know you'd never cheat on me.
分かってるよ 上原君が浮気なんかしないって よいつ
I know that, but I still don't like it.
でも分かってるけど やっぱイヤなの
I don't like feeling all jealous.
こんなふうに モヤモヤするのとか
I don't like being worried.
不安になってる自分が
I want to believe that you'd never, ever do such a thing,
絶対大丈夫って 上原君のこと信じたいけど
but...
でも...
I just can't be that confident.
私にはそんな自信 持てないよ
Nao.
吉川
Look at this.
(上原) これ
It was taped to your locker at school.
(上原)学校のお前のロッカーに 貼ってあった
Oh, my god.
何これ
You know...
(上原)だから
when things like this happen...
こうなったらやっぱ
I've been thinking about what to do.
いろいろ考えたんだけど
Let's move somewhere together.
(上原)一緒に引っ越すか
Together?
一緒に?
Yeah.
うん
There you go crying again.
ま~た泣く
I can't help it.
だって こつ
Silly girl.
(上 )パーカ 原
Hey! Darn you!
あつもう
I know you want to move,
引っ越しするって言ったけど
but who would rent to a couple of high school kids like us?
高校生の私たちに 貸してくれるとこなんてあるのかな
Besides, I don't want to give in to whoever is doing this.
それに 私負けたくないんだよね
Moving away is just what they want!
引っ越しするって 犯人の思うツボでしょ 田う
So I think we need to--
そしたらやっぱり 犯人をさ
Don't you even think about trying to catch this person.
捕まえようとか考えてんなら 絶対にやめろよ
You have no idea what they're like.
相手どんな奴か分かんねえし
I see.
(ルミ子)そうですか それで引っ越しを
Yes.
はい
But we're still minors.
でも未成年だし
So I was wondering if you could show us a place
大家さんに僕らだけでも 借りられる物件を
that would rent even to us.
紹介してもらえないかと思って
Uehara, you've lost some weight, haven't you?
上原君は 少し痩せましたねえ
I have?
え?
You're working hard at your jobs too, aren't you?
バイトも頑張ってるんですね
Yes.
まあ
If you move again, it will cost a lot of money.
また引っ越すとなると こ51つ 費用も大変ですね
I understand your situation,
事情は分かりましたが これを機会に
but maybe you should take this chance to live separately.
別々に暮らすことを 考えたらどうですが?
If you keep living together,
これ以上 一緒に暮らしていると
you two might suffer
あなたたちが傷つくことが またあるかもしれない
Thank you for worrying about us.
ご心配はありがたいです
But... living apart defeats the whole point.
でも別々じゃ意味ないんです
It's worth it, even if it means losing weight.
痩せるくらい全然平気です
OK.
うん
My phone!
携帯
Where is it?
え
What's she doing?
(一星)あいつ何やって
Take that!
や-!
Nao!
吉川
Who is this guy?
何者だ?こいつ
Yu?
(まみ)優君!?
What on earth are you doing here?
何やってんの? こんなところで
So you're the one?
あなただったの?
It's all your fault, two timing her like that.
お前が悪いんだぞ こて 二股かけて
You've been making her cry.
こいつのこと泣かせるから
What?
え?
I thought that if they broke up, then you'd stop crying over him.
(千崎)上原が彼女と別れれば まみが泣くこともないと思って
What in the world are you talking about?
(まみ)優君何言ってんの?
Isn't this guy your boyfriend?
いやだって
What? Is that true?
(一星)え?そうなの?
Are you kidding?
ありえねえし
You're so stupid!
バカ!
Mami had been acting odd for a while,
少し前から まみの様子が変だったから
so I followed her.
後つけたら…
She would buy food and visit this building.
食材買っては このマンションに出入りして
You were following me? You're crazy.
(まみ)尾行してたの? あきれた
You were sad because he cheated on you.
(千崎)浮気されたって こつ 泣いてんの見て
I couldn't ignore it.
ほっとけるわけないだろ!
So you thought Uehara was my boyfriend?
それで上原君を 彼氏だと思い込んだの?
He was your first love, right?
だって現に こつ お前の初恋の相手だろ上原は
That was so long ago.
いつの話よ
That's why you blackmailed him? Wow! You're a real screw up.
(一星)それで脅迫状って 完全にとばっちりだな
This pisses me off.
許せねえ
For the longest time, you've been pissing me off too!
俺だってお前だけは こつ ずっと許せねえって思ってた
In elementary school,
小学生の時まみが初めて渡した 本命チョコ断っただろ!
Oh, Yu!
優君...
I'm sure you can't understand my frustration.
(千崎) この悔しさお前には 分からないだろうけどな
So basically, her first love was Uehara,
(一星) つまり彼女の初恋が上原で
and your first love was her.
あんたの初恋が彼女ってことか
It's sure hard to get over your first love.
引きずるなあ初恋は
I really am sorry about this.
本当にごめんなさい
I did this all on my own.
俺が勝手にしたことだから
So go ahead and tell the police, or the school.
警察でも 学校にでも言ってくれ
I'm ready for whatever happens.
それぐらい覚悟はできてる
Forget it.
もういいよ
But if you ever try anything funny again,
でももし また何か変なことしたら
I'll make you pay.
今度は絶対許さねえからな
You sure you want to let him go?
(一星)おいいいのかよ このまま帰して
-He's broken the law-- -Forget about it.
これ立派な犯罪だぞ (上原)いいんだよ
Let's go, Yu.
(まみ)優君行こ
Wait!
待って
Apologize!
謝って
Apologize to Uehara.
ちゃんと 上原君に謝ってください
-Forget it, Nao. -I can't!
(上原)吉川もういいって (菜緒)よくない!
You called him a scumbag.
上原君に 最低な奴って言ったこと
Apologize to him for that!
ちゃんと謝ってください
I'm sorry.
悪かった
I envy those two.
いいよねあの2人
You can tell that they're together because they truly love each other.
本当に好きで 一緒にいるんだなっていうのが
No wonder I feel this way.
だからかな
I thought I could share the happiness he feels
上原君と一緒にいると
if I am with Uehara.
幸せ分けてもらえるような 気がしちゃう
I hurt his girlfriend too.
彼女さんにも 悪いことしちゃった
I'm a terrible person.
本当最低
If you're a terrible person, what does that make me?
(千崎)お前が最低だったら 脅迫状出した俺どうなんだよ
Good question.
確かに
Is that the guy?
あいつか?
Forget it!
いいの
-But-- -Just forget about it.
(千崎)でも (まみ)もういいの
I want you to dump him.
(千崎)もう別れろよ
Don't date guys that cheat.
浮気するような男と 付き合うな
You sure talk big.
偉そうに
Wait up, would you?
仟崎) ちょっと待て なあ
That settles that.
これで一件落着だな
No problem.
おう
OK, thanks for letting me stay here.
じゃあ世話になりました
You can come again anytime--
あつまた何かあったら いつでも来てね
Don't ever come again!
二度と来んな
Later.
じゃあな
Yeah. Bye.
(菜緒) うんバイバイ
It's just that
(菜緒)だって
we solved the blackmail problem,
脅迫状も解決したし
and Issei and his dad have made up,
いっちゃんもおやっさんと 仲直りできたし
and Yu's student teaching is over.
千崎先生の教育実習も 終わったし
It's finally just us two.
やっと2人きりだな
Uehara!
上原君
Huh?
あれ?
-Where did he go? -I'm leaving now.
あれ?あれ? (上原)先行くぞ
What? Hey! Wait a minute!
えっちよっ… ぇつらよつ. ちょっと待ってよ!
Wait for me, Uehara!
待ってよ上原君
Wait up!
ちょっと待って
-Oh, Nao. -Are you all right?
(光石)菜緒 (まり )大丈夫? な
So the blackmailing isn't solved.
脅迫状は 解決したんじゃなかったのか
What's happening at school is a different person.
学校での嫌がらせは 別ってことみたいだな
Do you think it's true that Nao and Uehara are living together?
(弥生)本当かな? 上原君と吉川さんが同棲って
Quit saying that crap!
のぞみ (希) うるさいな
It's total bull shit.
んなわけないじゃん
What are you going to do about this?
どうするつもり?
About what?
(EPT)
The rumors about living together.
同棲の噂だよ
Oh, that.
ああ...
You're an idiot if you think you can just ignore it.
しらばっくれときや どうにかなると思ってんなら甘いよ
I'm not ignoring it.
思ってねーよ
I'm telling you this because I'm Nao's friend.
(希) 吉川さんの友達として言うけど
I don't care how it affects you.
上原の立場なんか どうでもいい
I mean, you're a guy, after all.
だって こつ あんたは男だからいいよ
But with rumors like that,
でもああいう噂が立ったら
do you have any idea what happens to a girl's reputation?
女のほうが 何て言われるか分かってんの?
-Yeah, I do. -No, you don't!
分かってるよ (希)分かってない!
When all your girl fans start spouting lies,
あんたのファンの女とかが あることないこと言い始めて
it could easily end up hurting Nao!
吉川さんが傷つくかもしんないって 言ってんだよ
I've called this meeting about this morning's trouble.
(教頭)お集まりいただいたのは 今朝の騒ぎの件です
Uehara would never do anything like that.
(教師1)あの上原君に限って
But "Where there's smoke, there's fire."
(教師2) しかし火のないところに。 と言いますし
I want you to check the truth behind this, just to make absolutely certain.
(教頭)念のため慎重に 事実確認をお願いします
Huh? I thought you were at work.
あれ上原君バイトは?
-I'm going now. -Oh, I see.
(上原)今から (菜緒)そっか
-Uhm... -Yes?
仩原)あのさ (菜緒)ん?
I need to talk to you.
話があるんだけど るんに
About those posters?
いたずらのこと?
It doesn't bother me at all. I'm completely used to it.
私全然大丈夫だよ そういうの慣れっこだし
What is it, Uehara?
上原君?
Nao.
吉川
Yes?
ん?
I... want to live alone.
俺一人暮らしがしたいんだ
What?
え